A Guide to the Records of the Appalachian Student Organizing Committee, 1964-1975
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
Records of the Appalachian Student Organizing Committee, 1964-1975 (bulk 1971-1974)
Special Collections, Virginia Tech, Blacksburg, Va.
RG 31/14/10
12.4 Cubic Feet; 10 boxes; 1 oversize folder
The Appalachian Student Organizing Committee (or Appalachian Student Committee) was an approved student organization at the Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University in the early 1970s. The collection consists primarily of the papers of David Tice and Allan Cox, student organizers of the Appalachian Student Organizing Committee. Materials include correspondence, clippings files, small-press and local publications on Appalachian issues, petitions, and notes and drafts. The materials in the collection deal with various topics, including strip mining and land use issues, poverty, health care and free clinics, coal mining and coal miners, strikes, local political races, issues at Virginia Tech, and the Vietnam War and other national and international issues.
Appalachian Student Organizing Committee. Virginia Tech Chapter
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Acquisition Information
The collection was donated in September 1989.
Administrative History
The Appalachian Student Organizing Committee (or Appalachian Student Committee) was an approved student organization at the Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University in the early 1970s. The organizations' mission was to raise awareness about Appalachian issues and provide support for other grassroots organizations in the Appalachian region. The coordinators of the organization were David Tice and Allan Cox. David Tice was a member of the Class of 1974.
Scope and Content
The collection consists primarily of the papers of David Tice and Allan Cox, student organizers of the Appalachian Student Organizing Committee. Materials include correspondence, clippings files, small-press and local publications on Appalachian issues, petitions, and notes and drafts. The materials in the collection deal with various topics, including strip mining and land use issues, poverty, health care and free clinics, coal mining and coal miners, strikes, local political races, issues at Virginia Tech, and the Vietnam War and other national and international issues. The collection also include materials from other organizations whose mission overlapped with that of the ASOC, these organizations include Operation Coal Mining and the Appalachian Regional Resource Committee.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged into two series:
Series I consists of records, correspondence, and subject files and is arranged in alphabetical order by folder title.
Series II consists of publications and is arranged in alphabetical order by title.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Local/Regional History and Appalachian South; University Archives; University History
Places:
Blacksburg (Va.); Montgomery County (Va.)
Organizations:
Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University; Appalachian Student Organizing Committee. Virginia Tech Chapter
Contents List
- Series I: Records and subject files
  - Agricultural Extension Project, 1964-1974 (bulk 1971-1974) (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
  - "Appalachian Commonwealth" - Newsletter for the Appalachian Student Committee (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Appalachian Issues - Race and Racism, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Appalachian Peoples' Declarations (Appalachian Political Action Caucus), 1972 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Appalachian Movement Groups - directory, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Appalachian Issues - Oil, Energy, and Economic Development, 1967-1974 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Appalachian Issues - Education, 1967-1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Appalachian Issues - Advocacy and Awareness Campaigns, 1970-1973 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Appalachian Peoples' Free Clinic, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Appalachian Peoples' Service Organization, 1965-1974 (Box 1, Folder 11, Folder 1)
  - Appalachian Power Company, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Appalachian Regional Resource Center, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Appalachian Regional Resource Directory, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Appalachian Research and Defense Fund, Inc., 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Appalachian Resource Project (Tennessee), 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Appalachian Stripmining Information Service, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 17-19)
  - Appalachian Student Committee, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Appalachian Student Organizing Committee, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Appalachian Student Organizing Committee - Conflicts with University Administration, 1970-1974 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Appalachian Student Organizing Committee, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Appalachian Student Organizing Committee - Faculty Advisory Board, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Appalachian Student Organizing Committee - Fundraising, 1971-1974 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Appalachian Student Organizing Committee - Student Lists by Department (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Appalachian Studies, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Appalachian Support Committee - Richmond, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Attica Brigade, 1974, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Bland County - Power Structure Studies, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Blue Ridge Dams, 1975, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Blue Ridge Project, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Boise Cascade - Corporate Information, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Bootleg Coal, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Brookside - Harlan County, Kentucky, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 36-37)
  - Brown Lung, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Buffalo Creek - Man-made Disaster, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 1-3)
  - Campaign Continental, 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Campus Christian Life Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Chile and Central Intelligence Agency, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 6-7)
  - Coal Company Information, 1972, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Coal Leasing, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Coal Mining, 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Coal's Future, 1968, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Communitas, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Community Action Group - Directory, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Community Economic Development, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Community Free Clinic of Blacksburg, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - The Conference on Appalachian Struggle for Self-Government, March 3-5, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 16, Folder 1)
  - Conferences and Non-University Affiliated Organizations, 1970-1973 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Congress, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Consumer Protection, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Council of the Southern Mountains, 1970-1974 (Box 2, Folder 20-22)
  - Cox, Allen, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Cox, Allen and Tice, David - Correspondence and Notes, 1972-1974, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Cumberland, Kentucky - Mudslide, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Dickenson County, Virginia (see also: Pittston Company), 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Directory of Appalachian Resources - Forms, 1970, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Dominion Bankshares Corporations, 1970-1972 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Dupont Dynasty and Niagra Falls Strike, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Eastern Associated Coal Corporation, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Economic Priorities Report, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Economic Report - Conglomerate Merger Performance: an Empirical Analysis of Nine Corporations, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Energy Crisis, 1973-1975 (Box 3, Folder 1-3)
  - Episcopal Diocese: Appalachian Division, 1973-1975 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Equity Life Insurance, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Extension News, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Exxon, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Family Planning pamphlets, 1969-1972, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Farah Strike, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Farm Labor and Unions, 1970-1973 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Flood Relief, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Floyd County - Power Structure Studies, 1973, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - FMC Chemicals, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Forests and Appalachia, 1969-1974 (Box 3, Folder 15-16)
  - Forestry Service - Virginia Forested Land Ownership, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 17-18)
  - Forestry Student Group and Newsletter, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Free Clinics, 1971-1973 (Box 3, Folder 20-21)
  - Frontlash, 1971-1973 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Fuller, Fred H., 1973, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Gasification of Coal, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - General Information, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Georgia-Pacific Corporations, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Georgia Power Project, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Giant Earth Movers in Egypt Valley, 1972, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Hahn Commission, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Health, 1973-1975 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Highlander Center, 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Hightower Reprint - to be layed out, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Housing/Property Ownership, 1970, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Humble Oil, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Impeachment of President Nixon, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 6, Folder 1)
  - Information Received from Directory Replies, 1970-1972 (Box 4, Folder 7-8)
  - International Bank for Reconstruction and Development, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Island Creek Coal Company, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Kahn, Si, 1973, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Kennecott Copper Corporation, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Labor, 1968-1974 (Box 4, Folder 13-14)
  - Land Use, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - League for Industrial Democracy (LID), 1971-1974 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Land Reform, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Library Resources, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Mailing List and Directory Information, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Maine - Land Trusts, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Martin County, Kentucky, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - May Day, 1971, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 22-23)
  - McGovern, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Media, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Medical Issues and Health Insurance, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Middle East Issues, 1973-1975 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Miners' Energy Strike, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Miners for Democracy, 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Miners - Virginia, 1971-1974 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Mining - General, 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 31-32, Folder 1)
  - Mining - Health and Safety, 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 33, Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Mining vs. Society, 1971-1973 (Box 5, Folder 2-3)
  - Montgomery County- Power Structure Studies, 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Music, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Mount Rogers Development Research, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Mount Rogers - Forest Service, 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Mount Rogers - Funding, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Nashville, Tennessee, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Nationalized Mines, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Native Americans - Correspondence and Pamphlets, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 11-13)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity - War on Poverty, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Organizations - Appalachian Advocacy, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Organizing, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Paid Bills, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - People's Bicentennial, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 18-19)
  - Peoples Development Working Papers, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Physicians Committee for Miners Health and Safety - Press Release of Dr. I.E. Buff, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Pikesville Hospital Strike, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Pittston Company - Annual Report, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Pittston Company - Stockholders Meeting, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 24-25)
  - A Preliminary Approach to the Measurement of the Local Impact of Merger Activity, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Prisons, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Radio Free People, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Regional Economic Development Commission, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Religion and Appalachia, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Resources Acquired, 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Resource to be Received, 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Responses - Appalachian Organizations Directory, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Revenue Sharing, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Richlands Hospital Strike, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Right to Work, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Rockefeller, John D., 1971 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Role in Economy, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Russo, Anthony J., n.d. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Salaries of 1971 College Graduates Paid by Virginia Employers, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Save Our Kentucky, Inc., 1971 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Socialist Workers Party, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Social Responsibilities - Corporations, 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 7-8)
  - South African Coal, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Southwest Virginia - Newsclippings, 1972, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Speakers, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 11-12)
  - Statements and Working File, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Stripmining Information, 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 14-19)
  - Stripmining - Legislation, 1972-1975 (Box 6, Folder 20-21)
  - Stripmining - Resistance, 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Stripmining Study, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Stripmining - Virginia, 1972-1975 (Box 6, Folder 24-25)
  - Stripmining - West Virginia, 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Student Organizations, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Taxation - Mineral Properties, 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Technology vs. Culture, 1968-1973 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Tenants Union, 1971-1974 (Box 7, Folder 4-6)
  - Tennessee Valley Authority, 1970-1974 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Tenure, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Textile Workers Union of America - Radford FMC Plant, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - To Be Printed - Ready, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Total Action Against Poverty - Roanoke Valley, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 11, Folder 1)
  - Tourism, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Truckers' Strike, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Union Carbide and Foote Mineral, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - United Mineworkers of America - District 28 elections, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - United States Steel Corporation - Annual Report, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - United Steel Workers of America, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - University Employees, 1971-1974 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Vietnam, 1973-1975 (Box 7, Folder 19-20)
  - Virginia Advisory Legislative Council - Stripmining Committee and Citizens Committee on Stripmining, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Virginia Government, 1974, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University - Appalachian Issues, 1972, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University - Mining Engineering Department, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University - News Service, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University - Research Division, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University - University Administration, 1970-1974 (Box 7, Folder 27-28)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University - Water Resource Center and Sea Grant, 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Voter Registration - Montgomery County, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Welfare, 1971-1973 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - West, Don, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - World Population Problems, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Yippie News Service, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Young Men's Christian Association - World Alliance - Participacion Mexico, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 35-36)
  - Young World Development, 1971-1973 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Youth Grants for the Humanities, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - The Youth Project - Annual Report, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Series II: Publications, articles, and pamphlets
  - Action Power, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - AFL-CIO News, November 1974 - December 1974 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) - pamphlets, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - An analysis of stripmining methods and equipment selection, May 29, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Appalachia's People, Problems, and Alternatives, February 1972 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Appalachian Lookout, October 1969 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Appalachian Movement Press - pamphlets, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Appalachian News Service, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Appalachian Outlook, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Birth Control Handbook, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Catholic Committee of Appalachia, n.d. (Folder 1)
  - Coal Facts, January 28, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Coal Patrol, 1971-1973 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - The Consortium Guide, Fall 1973 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Critical Mass, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 4, Folder 1)
  - "Energy Crisis in America," Congressional Quarterly, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - The Corporate Examiner, 1973-1975 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - The Cultivator's Handbook of Marijuana, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - "People Speak Out on Stripmining," Council of the Southern Mountains, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Energy, Economics, and Our Environments, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Energy Reporter: Federal Energy Administration Citizen Newsletter, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Facing-up: Statistical Data on Virginia's Public Schools, January 1971 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - "Facts About Coal in the United States," Environmental Policy Group, April 1974 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Feed Kids - Food News from the Childrens' Foundation, October 1974 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Fight Back, November 1973 - April 1974 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Forest Service and Appalachia, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Full-Tilt: A Community Broadside Magazine, Richmond, VA, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Grass Roots, April 1974 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Gulf Oilmanac, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - The Hawkeye, May 1974 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Health Rights News, December 1971 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - "Highway Program Shows Limited Progress Towards Increasing Accessibility to and through Appalachia," Report to Congress, May 21, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Journal of Current Social Issues, Spring 1974 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Latin America and Empire Report, 1973-1975 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Le Journal Jaune, October 1970 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Liberation News Service, 1969-1971 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Maine Land Advocate, December 1972 - April/May 1975 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Maine Times, October 1974 - December 1974 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - "The March on Washington - 10 Years Later" by Bayard Rustin, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Mid-Appalachian Environmental Service Newsletter, February 1973 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Miners Journal, March 1973 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - The Miner's Voice, June 1970 - July/August 1972 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Monthly Review of Coal Mining and Quarrying, 1971-1975 (Box 8, Folder 31-33)
  - The Mountain Community, 1972-1975 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - The Mountain Eagle, November 1971-January 1973 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Mountain Journal, November 1974 - January 1975 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Mountain Liberator, November 1971 - March 1972 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Mountain Life and Work, 1969-1972 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - The Mountain Messenger, March 1972-April 1972, January 1974 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - New World, September 1971 - May 1972 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers - National Oil Bargaining Policy, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - The Operation Human Dignity Voice, October 30, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - The Paper, May-June 1971 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - The Paperworker, December 1974 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - People's Appalachia, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - People's Bicentennial Commission - Common Sense, 1974, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - People and Land, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - People and Taxes, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Publications and articles - Appalachia-related, 1971-1972, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Public Housing: An Economic Evaluation, March 1973 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Public Interest Letter, June 1974 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Quaker Service Bulletin, Winter 1973 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Shot Tower, December 1971 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - The Southern Patriot, April 1970 - February 1975 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Understanding City Budgets, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Union Democracy Review, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - United Labor Action, October 1974, June-July 1975 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Up from Under: By, For, and About Women, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Vantage Point, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Virginia Minerals, May 1972 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Virginia State Department of Health - Major Activities, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - The Virginia Weekly, September 1970, April 1972 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - What Mining Means to the United States, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Win, July 18, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Workers World, October 18, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Work Force - published by Vocations for Social Change, March-April 1973 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Young World Day Newsletter - Southeast, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 49)